Hello, Problem Solver 68.
Rikuhachima speaking.
Yes, of course.
We specialize in intelligence
as well as muscle for conflict.
(An Evil a Day)
We'll do the crime
if you've got the dime.
Very well. Understood.
Problem Solver 68 is
on the job.
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
Ayane, what is this?
I found this yesterday
inside one of the Kata-Kata
Helmet Gang's armored vehicles.
According to my investigation,
these shells are supposed
to be totally prohibited.
How did the Helmet Gang
even get this kind of stuff?
The black market, maybe?
Could be.
But wouldn't they be difficult
to find, let alone afford?
Sounds like they've got
themselves a backer.
By investigating how
these parts were distributed,
we could pin down who's
helping the Helmet Gang.
Right.
Plus we might figure out
the reason they've been targeting
our school over and over again.
So, everyone.
Let's start our morning meeting.
Sensei will also
be joining us today
so please be serious for once.
What? You make it sound
as if we're never serious!
Welcome to Abydos,
Sensei.
Thanks!
Are there any suggestions
on what the Foreclosure Task Force
should do for our next move?
Me, me!
First-year Kuromi Serika
has the floor.
As the Foreclosure Task
Force's accountant,
let me remind you all that our
school is on the brink of bankruptcy.
Just catching wanted criminals,
or taking on part-time jobs
won't nearly be enough.
So I say let's go for the jackpot!
And that jackpot is...
This right here!
(Germanium Bracelet)
Overruled.
Serika, that's a
pyramid scheme.
It'll never work.
(Germanium Bracelet)
No way...
I already bought two of them.
Serika's a little gullible.
It's so cute!
So, anyone else?
- Here, here!
-All right.
Third-year
Takanashi Hoshino, speaking.
Please, please be serious.
Our school's biggest problem...
is that we only have five of us here.
Hm.
A school's strength
lies in its student body.
Therefore...
we need more students.
Wise words, but what's your plan?
Easy peasy.
We hijack buses from other schools.
What?!
Stealing school buses?
We threaten the passengers
to sign transfers
if they want to get off the bus.
Then watch as our
enrollment numbers skyrocket.
Sounds like a solid plan.
Who's the target?
Trinity? Or Gehenna?
Millennium?
Overruled!
Take this more seriously!
Will the students really
sign transfers under duress?
Not to mention how the other schools'
student councils would respond.
Yeah, you're right...
Please remember to think
before you speak, everyone.
Hey, Ayane. I have an idea.
Speak, Second-year
Sunaookami Shiroko.
Let's rob a bank.
What?!
N-Not another crime!
It's the surest method.
(Abydos First Central Bank)
Our target is the
First Central Bank downtown.
I've already scouted
the location of the vault,
the guards' patrols, and
the route of the cash trucks.
And of course...
Oh my!
Did you make these yourself, Shiroko?
We'll look just like masked wrestlers.
You really thought this through, Shiroko.
This looks great.
Life's all about shooting your shot.
Right, Serika?
Are you kidding me?
She's right. Overruled!
Absolutely no crimes!
You know that sort of thing
is wrong, so stop sulking.
Everyone, please suggest
ideas we can actually do.
Hey! It's my turn!
Go, Second-year
Izayoi Nonomi.
No more crimes or scams please.
Of course!
It's neither a crime nor a scam,
but legal, wholesome, and helpful!
Nonomi!
How about we become...
...idols!
High school idols!
-Idols?
-That's right.
Being idols is a surefire way
to revive the school.
Once we make our big debut...
Overruled!
Why not? I already came up
with our ending pose.
Did any of you actually
think about this?
Keep this up, and you
can forget about this meeting!
Hold on, Ayane.
How about we let Sensei chip in?
Huh? Me?
Yeah, Sensei.
Which of today's ideas did you like?
W-Which one?
Naturally, the bank robbery.
No, it was the bus hijacking.
Idols please!
-M-Maybe the idols...
-You all...
Enough is...
...enough!
We made Ayane mad.
Target acquired.
Hm.
Aru, did we really
have to go so far
over a simple retrieval job?
Call me Boss when
we're working,
Chief Mutsuki.
Sometimes you have to crack
eggs to make an omelette.
Don't fret over
every minor detail.
That's what real outlaws do.
Aru's being a weirdo again.
Uh, Boss...
Wh-What's wrong,
Department Head Kayoko?
The client wanted the target
brought back unharmed, right?
Of course. Is there a problem?
Wh-What?
Boss, are we...
No pay for us.
Wh-Wh-What?
What did you say?!
We said sorry, Ayane.
The ramen's on us.
So don't be angry.
I'm not angry.
Let me get that for you.
Don't treat me like a child.
-Have some more meat, Ayane.
-Fine.
Welcome!
How many are in your group?
Pardon.
What is the cheapest item on your menu?
That'd be our Shiba Seki Ramen at 580 yen.
It's our delicious
house special.
Thank you!
Aru, the special here
costs 580 yen.
Finally, some food
under 600 yen.
See, everything worked out fine.
Just as planned.
Welcome! Table for four?
Right this way.
Oh, no.
We're only ordering one bowl,
so take out is fine.
But you're already here.
Please have a seat and eat.
We have plenty of room.
What friendly staff.
You know, what? Why not.
Oh, waiter.
Four pairs of chopsticks, please.
Eh? Wait a minute...
Are you four
sharing a single bowl?
S-Sorry.
We're all flat broke.
It's okay, you don't
have to apologize.
You don't understand.
No money means no life.
We don't deserve to live.
We are less than insects.
Sorry for being penniless insects.
Haruka, people are staring.
What are you saying?
Being broke is not a sin.
Right, Master?
Sure thing.
Money comes and goes.
You girls are students, right?
Y-Yes.
But you pooled your money
just to have my ramen.
That warms my heart.
I'll get cooking.
Please take a seat while you wait.
Y-Yes.
I think they're overdoing it a bit.
Yeah, we're not
always this broke, right?
It's only because Aru
is terrible with money.
We didn't make a dime
from our last gig.
Then we had to drain our savings
hiring muscle for the next one.
And yet here we are about to
enjoy delicious ramen, right?
Just as planned.
But Boss...
...is our next target strong enough
that we need that many people?
That's...
I'm convinced Aru
doesn't even know herself.
So she hired a whole
squadron out of fear.
Who says I'm scared?
Failure is not an option.
Expect the unexpected!
You all know that's
Problem Solver 68's motto.
I don't remember us
having that motto.
That's because
she just came up with it.
Shut up!
Thank you for waiting.
Wh-What is this?
What a huge bowl!
Looks like enough
for ten people.
Is this the right order?
We can't afford
something like this.
Nope, this is all yours.
A Shiba Seki Ramen for 580 yen.
Right, Master?
I measured out
the ingredients wrong...
...so you girls can
eat the extras.
I didn't expect this...
...but if he worked so hard,
we can't waste it, can we?
Let's eat, Aru!
Of course!
Thank you for the food!
So good!
Isn't it?
The ramen here's the best.
It really is.
I've eaten at a lot of
different restaurants.
But ramen this
delicious is a rarity.
Is that uniform from Gehenna Academy?
You came a long way to eat.
Y-Yes.
We're all regulars here.
Is that so?
-I envy you.
-Kayoko.
-Aren't they...
-Mmm.
They're Abydos students.
It's so nice to meet people
that I click with.
Unexpected encounters
like this...
...are what make
life interesting.
Agreed.
Aru still doesn't realize it?
Should we tell her?
No, it's funnier this way.
Well, take care.
(Shiba Seki Ramen)
Good luck making money out there.
Same to you as well.
I'll be rooting for you.
See ya!
Weren't they nice?
Uh, Boss...
Yes, Department Head Kayoko?
Did you get a good look at their uniforms?
Uniforms? What about them?
They're students from Abydos High School.
Wh-What?
What did you say?!
The look on your face.
That means they're our next target?
Should I pursue them?
No, they're gone already.
I figure we'll take
them on soon enough.
You can cut loose then, Haruka.
R-right.
N-No way!
I can't believe they
were our next target.
Don't sweat it.
"We'll do the crime
if you've got the dime."
That's our motto, right?
So what's the problem?
You're right, but...
The Boss is a giant softy.
This is gonna be a pain.
Now that won't do, Aru.
You're the boss that charts our course.
Let's go!
Eh? Is that what you all
got up to yesterday?
Yep! We became friends with some
students from Gehenna.
They were really wowed
by the master's ramen.
Right?
The master's ramen really is the best.
What were they like?
Apparently they run some
kind of business—
(Urgent Warning
Intruders detected.)
The monitors south of the school
detect an armed force approaching.
Is it the Helmet Gang again?
No.
Looks like...
a mercenary company.
Are you ready?
Of course.
We'll fight whoever,
just no overtime.
Especially at your pay.
Quiet about that!
Now then, let's go attack
Abydos High School.
Roger.
Weren't they at Shiba Seki Ramen?
Nonomi?
Sensei, those are the Gehenna students
we mentioned earlier.
You traitors!
To think we even gave you
an extra large ramen!
Ingrates!
Thanks a bunch yesterday.
But that was then.
This is now.
You know we're broke right?
We don't mix business with pleasure.
We were paid for this job,
so we have to work.
Indeed, it's just who we are.
Problem Solver 68!
I see. So you lot are hired guns.
You're students! You should have
more wholesome part-time jobs!
This isn't just some part-time job,
it's a serious business!
We even have proper titles, too.
I'm the Boss.
She's the Chief,
and this is our Department Head.
You're making us look silly.
Who hired you?
That's a trade secret.
Guess we'll have to make you talk.
We're just following orders.
Don't take it so personally.
Everyone, let's go!
Right.
-Let's make this quick.
-Sure.
Stop resisting and just
hand over the school.
We'll never do that.
Now, Kayoko!
Nice, Mutsuki.
Drop your weapon.
Serika!
Don't worry, I'm fine.
I have you now.
Geez.
C4.
Claymore.
Shiroko?!
I'm all right.
That was close.
We're cornered.
Take this!
They're no pushovers.
Even if we can match their strength,
we can't match their numbers.
In that case...
Everyone,
I have a plan.
Listen closely.
Sensei.
Shiroko, there's something
I need you to do.
They still haven't surrendered?
Keep shooting until they do!
Here we go.
-Wh-What?
-Why are they so fired up?
That hurt!
We're not just gonna sit and take it.
Just give up.
Aru.
Haruka.
What's with the change in tactics?
Could it be...
Boss, watch out!
For what?!
Oh no.
-Boss!
-Aru!
We are Problem Solver 68!
We always get the job done.
Give up
and hand over your school.
No way.
Quitting time.
And we said no overtime.
That's our shift.
Yep.
N-Now wait a minute!
We're so close!
You said no overtime pay.
You guys handle it.
I'm beat.
-Wanna get some burgers?
-Sounds good.
Can I come too?
Seems mercenaries
never work for free.
They all left.
Guess we just lost.
We're in trouble now.
Think we should bail, Aru?
This battle isn't over.
Aru, you sound like
a B-movie supervillain.
Shut up. Run!
I mean, retreat!
Wait up, Aru!
Later!
What interesting girls.
What even was that?
Who knows...
I'm starving.
Now that everything's settled,
wanna grab something to eat?
-I'm in.
-Yep!
Will you treat us, Sensei?
H-Hold on! Let me
make sure I have the money!
Thanks a bunch!
I'll take a window seat on this journey to find
the place where my heart belongs
So I can see beyond this sorrow chasing me.
We were losing track of time without ever knowing why
With all those laughs we shared...
Even if...those moments were just ordinary.
Those days...
One more time, one time more,
Knowing they won't come around again!
If only I could stay light and beautiful
As the moon hanging in the bright noon sky.
Would that let me finally forgive
All those regrets we made so willfully?
We only recognize the important things
Once they're gone and lost out of sight.
We stretch up to the moon in the bright noon sky
Even though it will always be beyond our reach.
Oh, those unforgettable, beautiful days...
(Kaiser PMC Director
Rikuhachima Aru, Problem Solver 68)
What trash...
(Report on the failure to seize Abydos High)
It seems those Abydos girls are
more persistent
than our data suggests.
But data is always changing.
Don't worry.
I'll root out
this little error.